I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
"Knowing someone is reading this."
"Taitou Senior High School."
"Absolute Success!!"
That cool song was requested
by radio listener, Suikaman,
Neurofika's "Aikita."
It's been awfully chilly lately, huh?
To students studying for entrance exams,
please don't catch a cold.
Our next request comes
from Yukio Tanaka in Tokyo.
It's for you, Yukio.
"My World Down" by Dying Breed.
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
Creep!
Are you all right?
-Pervert!
-I'm okay, but my camera's dead.
I wanted some bittersweet memories
of the days of my youth,
so I had to take a bit of a risk...
-Hey Tanabe!
-Huh?
That rumor about Momo-chan...
that she used to work part-time
in a cabaret club in college...
Is it for real?!
It bothers me so much
I can't study at all!
Calm down guys.
Give me a little more time to check it out.
I'll find proof before graduation.
I swear it on my grandpa's good name.
Who's your grandpa?
He's a railway employee.
-Hmm...
Let's go.
-Yeah.
A cabaret club, huh?
And the one who got the idea for this
was Franz Schubert of Austria.
-And so...
-Huh?
Tanaka-kun!
Are you paying attention?
Umm...
Maybe you've been studying too hard.
You have to relax sometimes.
Yes.
-Which school do you wanna go to?
-Huh? Oh...
I'm trying for Tachi High.
I'm trying for Tokutake High.
Hey Tanaka...
-Hit me.
-Huh?
Haven't you wanted to hit me?
Err...Not anymore.
And before?
You can't hit me?
Coward!
What was that?
Your punch is like a girl's.
People who create things
must express their feelings clearly
or it's not good...
My old man used to say that.
So long.
Hyodo-kun!
See you around.
Yeah.
As expected, Momoko-sensei broke
into tears during graduation ceremonies.
And high school entrance exams
ended without much fanfare.
Yukio!
Hurry or you'll be late
for the entrance ceremony!
I know!
"Private Ichieda Academy
Senior High School"
From today, you are students
of Ichieda Academy
here to study,
participate in sports and clubs.
Osamu Kido, whose mentor,
Karl Goch, treated like a son...
"Anime Research Society"
Hey, you seem like one of our kind.
No thanks. I don't intend to join a club.
Hey Koyuki!
Hey Saku!
Look at your hair!
Well, I'm in high school now,
so I changed it.
Don't go trying to look sexy.
Huh?
Lemme at you!
-Hah!
-Hey!
Shaddup! Trying to act grown-up!
It's 100 years too early, kid!
Hey, that's mean, Chiba-kun! Stop it!
Geez! It took me an hour this morning.
Huh? One hour?
Senpai! I'm just not good
at signing up members!
Shut up! If our activities end up
in the red, it'll be your fault!
Moreover...the sign-up fee is too high.
-Umm...
-Huh?
Umm...Kikata-kun...
You should give up already.
Yusuke, he's the one...
Yeah, I know.
He just up and left...
-I guess we'll be going, too...
-Hey!
You're Yukio Tanaka,
the sophomore in Group 4?
You'll pass out tickets in his place.
Why me?
Uh! Yeah!
You open up the door with negative aura
-Saku and I finished our entrance exams
-You open up the door with negative aura
-and we'll be concentrating
100% on the band.
-You say future is murky indeed...
-and we'll be concentrating
100% on the band.
-I'm sick of hearing gripe.
Open up the door with negative aura
-I can't keep practicing
on Saito-san's guitar forever...
-Open up the door with negative aura
-I can't keep practicing
on Saito-san's guitar forever...
-If you never change
-I can't keep practicing
on Saito-san's guitar forever...
-I think there is no way my life fizzle out...
-And I've been wanting my own guitar.
Oh yeah? Then I'll go
with you to shop around.
There's one I wanna see, too.
Really?
I'll catch up with you later.
What about you guys?
This is all I need.
You being sarcastic?
Say, don't you get nervous
going into a music store?
You'll get used to it.
So, what are you after?
A Stratocaster...Jaguar...
Jazz Master...
Explorer...SG...
Makes me want all of them!
-This one...a Kayama Yuzo
by Mosrite is good.
-Oh?
No need to rush into it.
We can check out other places.
You're right.
He dissed me!
Umm...
My friends and I are gonna start a band...
We need something called an effector.
Umm...My friend said something like
what Pink Floyd uses might work for us...
Do you even know what an effector is?
Not only that...get real.
You can't produce a sound like
Pink Floyd on a 5000-yen budget.
Oh, it doesn't really
have to be Pink Floyd...
Make up your mind!
Did you see last night's Time Machine?
Van Halen was on.
Yes.
-Ryusuke-kun...That clerk is scary.
-There's no one like them these days...
A lot of 'em are like that.
Excuse me...
I want to try out this
pretty Tiger-eye Les Paul.
Ryusuke-kun...this one says 'ask' on
the tag. How much do you think it is?
1,080,000 yen.
Huh?
That's vintage 1959 Les Paul
made by the legendary Tom Murphy.
Yeah...
Hmm...
Hey, keep your hands off!
I was going to use this as a down payment.
Just a minute...
Ryusuke-kun! How'd you
get so much money?
I was gonna go to the fish farm
after this to buy fish.
Takano-san...Y-You're amazing.
Okay, this guitar is prepped.
Koyuki, play.
Huh? Ryusuke-kun, you play.
Yeah?
Can't get a true sound
if it's wired like this.
H-How is it?
Yeah...so-so.
Hey, Ryusuke.
Huh? Takano-san.
Oh, Taira! It's been awhile.
Damn, your hair has grown.
Ah, this? I know. I used to be bald.
-How's Fire Joker?
-We disbanded last year.
Disbanded?
Yeah...
I was 27 when we formed the band
and I swore I wouldn't cut my
hair until we had a major debut.
-Ah...
-Hmm...
Where's Koyuki?
Huh? Where'd he go?
Weren't you together?
Yeah...for a bit.
Don't badmouth Kenji-san.
Huh?
He may not look it,
but he's tops in maintenance.
'Kay.
Hey, what's up?
Like it?
Try it out.
I feel...
I feel as though the guitar is calling me.
A Telecaster?
But you've got to wonder
what kind of condition it's in.
You're right.
Kenji-san...
Well, if you buy it,
I'll replace the bridge and peg.
Hmm...I'll even replace the pick-up.
Really?
But I...
...don't have the cash.
In the past, Taira came out to help
and really saved me a number of times.
That's not the reason, but I'm
willing to make you a special loan.
Thank you! I'll think about it.
Hey Koyuki...Play it.
G-Geez...I'm embarrassed
to play in front of you three.
Why'd you act so shy?
Well...
"Chinese Restaurant Sing Lung"
-Hurry it up.
-I'm sorry.
Tanaka-kun...The dumplings?
The customer is waiting.
Hey, Tanaka, put your back into it.
-Right!
-Hurry with the spring rolls!
Two more hours.
Ouchie!
Hey part-timer! I'm making
the soup, so crack the eggs.
Oh, right!
In this world, even someone
so amazing couldn't turn pro...
His hair was so long.
"Sant 'Himizu"
Ow...
Huh? If it isn't Tanaka-kun!
What're you doing?
I deliver papers.
By the way, are the tickets selling?
No...I've been busy
with band rehearsals
and haven't done a thing.
Hey, that's bad!
You have to help, too, Kikata-kun!
Oh, I have to deliver
my newspapers. See you!
Huh?
Hey! What's going on?
I told you, I was so busy,
I couldn't sell tickets.
Oh...
Come to the club office.
I warned him! This is bad! This is bad!
Is this club for light music?
-Of course!
-We all have perfect music sense.
Oh...
No, these guys aren't like Hyodo.
It's cool, huh? The Martin D45.
-Huh?
Yeah...it's great. That Marching.
Damn it!
You make me sick, just like Chiba!
-Do you know the Death Valley Bomb?
-No...
-What about Michinoku Driver?
-A little...
-Awright!
-Shiiki!
Chiba-kun!
Saku!
You're pitiful, Shiiki!
You shattered my dream of being
homeroom president three years in a row!
Hey, you've got it wrong!
It's not something I was hoping for...
Our teacher chose based on our grades.
You're the homeroom president?
Listen up, Shiiki...
If you ever lay your hands on Koyuki
or Saku you'll regret it big time.
Sorry...You took some knocks there.
-Nah...
-Umm...
-Huh?
Could you put me on your
list of persons to protect?
Who are you?
I'm hungry! Let's go eat ramen!
-Uh-huh...
Me too.
The other day, some cases of bullets
were sent to me with a letter.
"Fishing Hole"
Eddy, that sounds so crazy.
You got some manic groupie or somethin'?
No, no...no. I have a bad hunch.
The number of cases
were the same number
as bullet marks on Lucille's body.
Hey that means...
Yeah...
I think...he found out about that.
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Wash your face and take the challenge!
"Live 16 'Indies'"
Paul Newman is so cool!
I wanna be a hustler, too!